hoofoot.com 2018-08-23

# HooFoot - Latest Football Highlights

**Hoofoot Privacy Policy**

Updated May 10, 2018

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which HooFoot collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.HooFoot.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by HooFoot.

**Personal identification information  
**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information  
**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Cookies  
**  
Like many web sites, Hoofoot.com uses cookies to enhance your user experience (to remember your personal settings, for instance). Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. 

**Classification and types of cookies used**

The different types of cookies used can be classified according to various criteria: uptime, managing organization and purpose. 

According uptime of cookies on the user's browser, we can differentiate between session cookies and persistent cookies. Session Cookies are those used while the user browses the website and are retained for the time of shipping. They are used to store information on access and use of the site itself. Meanwhile, Persistent Cookies are those which are stored for a limited time the user's browser, even when it has finished browsing the page. 

According to the entity that manages and sets the cookies, we find the Own Cookies and Third Party Cookies. The Treasury Cookies are those set by the domain of the website visited by the user and only accesses the domain itself. They are typically used, among others, to remind the user in their successive visits to the website. Meanwhile, Third Party Cookies are those established and operated by domains other than the website itself accessed. They are generally used for tracking users in different sites with the aim to send users customized to your tastes and interests advertising. 

As a last type of classification, we find different types of cookies depending on their purpose: Technical Cookies, Cookies Analysis, the Rack Cookies Cookies and customization.

Techniques Cookies are those considered necessary for the proper functioning of the Website and the services offered therein. Some uses of these cookies could be remind users when browsing and remember the set selected by each user for further payment and purchase products. Analysis Cookies are used to study and learn anonymously on user behavior while surfing the web page. Some applications of the information collected by these cookies are used to explore aspects concerning the total visitors users and the products that generate attraction between users within the website. The Rack Cookies allow adapting the web advertising space to interest visitors effective users. And finally, Personalization Cookies allow the web site to use for each user a general set of predefined as may be the language or the type of browser used features.

Hoofoot.com uses cookies together to have a better knowledge of visitors to your web agina to suit the interests of its members. The set of Hoofoot.com work with others to improve data capture using these instruments does not authorize these third parties to use the data collected, except information that is intended to improve the website and services offered by Hoofoot.com

**Cookies Setting  
**  
Each user can set your browser to notify you when you are sending a Cookie is made or can disable the sending of all Cookies. The forms and characteristics in order to perform these actions vary depending on the browser you use, therefore all users to consult the characteristics of each modalities are recommended for possible and own ways of modifying shipping and storage Cookies.

In the event that the user disable all cookies might find impossibilities or difficulties in using the services offered on the website, as well as access to some content.

For the user to learn more about the configuration of your browser Cookies, we provide the following links below:

**Internet Explorer:** Tools -> Options -> Privacy -> Settings. To know further you cancontact [**Microsoft**](http://windows.microsoft.com/es-es/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11) or use the browser help. **Firefox:** Tools -> Options-> Privacy-> History-> Custom settings. To know further you cancontact [**Mozilla**](https://support.mozilla.org/es/products/firefox/privacy-and-security) or use the browser help. **Chrome:** Settings -> Advanced Options -> Privacy-> Content Settings. To know further you cancontact [**Google**](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=es&ref_topic=3421433) or use the browser help. **Safari:** Preferences -> Security. To know further you cancontact [**Apple**](http://www.apple.com/es/support/mac-apps/safari/) or use the browser help. 

**Advertising  
**  
Hoofoot.com primarily utilizes the Google Analytics web service to monitor usage patterns and statistics of this website. As a result when you browse this website, some identifiable information will be shared with Google in order to aggregate statistics. We encourage you to read the Google privacy policy to familiarize yourself with how Google can use this information.

**3rd Party Advertisements  
**  
We use third-party advertising powered by Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click here.

Our primary advertising is provided by Google Adsense who utilize the doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

**How we protect your information  
**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information  
**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Uses  
**  
If you submit personally identifiable information to us through HooFoot, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the HooFoot Site, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos, photos or send messages through the HooFoot Site and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos or photos that you submit to the HooFoot Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major HooFoot Site changes or for customer service purposes). We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the HooFoot Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the HooFoot Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

**Changes to this privacy policy  
**  
HooFoot.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms  
**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Information  
**  
For more information you may contact hoofoot through email form available on hoofoot.com
